var questions1 = [{
                'question': "\0 meta character does what?",
                'answer': "finds a nul character"
              },{
                'question': "7 values that make boolean false",
                'answer': "0<br>-0<br>null<br>\" \"<br>false<br>undefined<br>NaN <-- not a number"
              },{
                'question': "alert box syntax?",
                'answer': "alert(\"message\");"
              },{
                'question': "\\B meta character does what?",
                'answer': "find a match that is not at the beginning of a word (or returns null)<br>x=\"hello world\"<br>y=/\\Borld/g<br>document.write(x.match(y))--> orld"
              },{
                'question': "\\b meta character does what?",
                'answer': "used to find a match at the beginning or end of a word (if none null)<br>x=\"hello world\"<br>y=/\\bworld/g<br>document.write(x.match(y))--> world"
              },{
                'question': "syntax for line breaks in an alert box?",
                'answer': "\'\/n\' + \" here\""
              },{
                'question': "the last index in a string is?",
                'answer': "string.length-1"
              },{
                'question': "toUpperCase() method does what?",
                'answer': "converts a string to uppercase letters"
              },{
                'question': "What is the command to display a prompt?",
                'answer': "prompt(\"Text Here\");"
              },{
                'question': "How do you assign the value from a prompt to a string?",
                'answer': "var stringVar = prompt(\"Text Here\");"
              },{
                'question': "else if conditional syntax?",
                'answer': "if(condition) { code } <br>else if(condition) { code }"
              },{
                'question': 'Calling an external javascript file syntax?',
                'answer': "&lt;script type=\"text/javascript\" src=\"javascript.js\" &gt;"
              }, {
                'question':'Is javascript case sensitive?',
                'answer':"Yes!"
              },{
                'question': "javascript comment syntax?",
                'answer': "\/**\/ for multiple lines <br> \/\/ for a single line"
              },{
                'question': "If a variable is not a function and does not have var then it is?",
                'answer': "a global variable"
              },{
                'question': "can variables include other variables?",
                'answer': "yes"
              },{
                'question': "x=x+y is the same as what? or x=x\/y?",
                'answer': "x+=y or x\/=y"
              },{
                'question': "numbers + strings =? <br> 5+\"5\" = ?",
                'answer': "strings <br> 55"
              },{
                'question': "javascript starts counting on what?",
                'answer': "0"
              }

              ];